we're just going to create a new one the reason i cut out the last video is because i made some
last minute changes to this form just so that it would so that it like flows better when you use
it um so really bright red are these first two there now you can see okay um because these two
once you fill these two out it forces you to do them first but as a result of that it will
auto-populate all of these other different fields the seo and a checkout name all of the more
redundant ones or the more technical ones and you can edit them after it populates it's just a
you know trying to make it easier
so right right away it automatically populates the slug and that's because if you hover here
it tells you locks once saved so and it does auto save so when it says that it means if you manually
save it or if i was to like click out of this uh panel that would count as forcing a save basically
um
and now as i fill out the rest it should also fill out the rest so let's see
,
all these little numbers that count down there just to show you um best estimate of like best
practices so it'll turn red once you have about like five characters left and then it goes negative
once you're past it in the interest of time i'm just going to copy and paste this
to show you that these also just filled out really fast excuse me and the size of a t-shirt
um this little helper should remind you to yep
either right foot or inches or use the double quotes or single quotes just one automatically
puts pounds
all right
so